<resources>
    <string name="avatars_switch_another">Switch to another</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus1">The first rays of morning sunlight fall on the windowsill, awakening the sleeping earth. Birds sing cheerfully on the branches, and the gentle breeze rustles the leaves, making a rustling sound. Distant mountains are shrouded in mist, like an ink painting. The sounds of nature are so beautiful, as if telling endless stories.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus2">The kitchen is filled with the aroma of coffee, the spatula flipping eggs in the pan, making sizzling sounds. Bread turns golden in the oven, the sweet scent of jam intertwines with the bitterness of coffee. Sunlight streams through the window onto the dining table, breakfast preparations are orderly. This is my morning, filled with warmth and satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus3">Raindrops outside the window tap the glass, making soft sounds. I sit in the corner of a café, holding a cup of hot coffee, the aroma fills the air. Around me are whispers and the hum of coffee machines, occasionally the beep of a cash register. Rainy days always make people want to stop, to enjoy a moment of peace and warmth.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus4">The train slowly departs the platform, the scenery outside the window gradually becoming blurry. I lean against the window, listening to the friction between the wheels and the tracks, my thoughts drifting far away. Fields, villages, and mountains pass by one by one along the way, like a silent film. Passengers in the carriage converse in low voices, occasionally laughter can be heard. Such journeys always fill people with anticipation.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus5">I remember when I was young, my friends and I would run in the fields, chasing butterflies and dragonflies. As the sun sets, golden sunlight bathes the earth, our laughter echoes in the air. Those summers always felt so long, with the chirping of cicadas rising and falling, as if it would never end. Those carefree days still fill me with nostalgia.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus6">The city night is illuminated, neon lights cast colorful shadows on the streets. Traffic flows like a织, pedestrians hurry by, each with their own destination. Distant skyscrapers twinkle in the night sky, like countless stars fallen to earth. Such nights are always full of energy, as if they would never sleep.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus7">Snowflakes fall outside the window, blanketing the earth in a white coat. Tree branches are laden with snow, as if adorned with white blossoms. I stand by the window, watching children have snowball fights and build snowmen, their laughter echoing in the air. Winter snow scenes always bring a sense of peace and beauty.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus8">When I was young, I loved summer evenings best. Grandpa would sit with me in the courtyard, fanning with a straw fan, telling me stories about the stars. Those twinkling starlights seemed to hold endless secrets. To this day, it remains the warmest memory in my heart.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus9">When the spring breeze brushes the willow tips, tender buds waltz on the branches; summer cicadas hide in the shade, weaving sultry afternoons with their chirps; autumn rain taps the window panes, carrying the sweet fragrance of osmanthus to moisten the pages of books; winter snow covers the eaves, and the crackling of the炉火 harbors fairy tales. The changing seasons are like a poem on repeat, each stanza etched with the code of time.</string>
    <string name="avatars_corpus10">The dough spins and expands in the palm, the air pockets from fermentation resembling the rhythm of breathing. After three hours of simmering, the beef bone broth shimmers with amber ripples, and the moment freshly ground Sichuan pepper is sprinkled, steam carries the spiciness into the nostrils. Cooking is an art of precise chaos—subtle differences in heat, the balance of ingredients yin and yang, ultimately blossoming on the tongue into an epic beyond taste.</string>
</resources>